<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on </title>
    <link>https://matthewemes.com/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017 Matthew Emes. Except where explicitly noted, content on this site is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License (see https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://matthewemes.com/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Azure CLI to Chromebook</title>
      <link>https://matthewemes.com/2017/09/installing-azure-cli-to-chromebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewemes.com/2017/09/installing-azure-cli-to-chromebook/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was asked to contribute to a white-paper for Azure container
services and as part of that task I naturally wanted to install the
CLI. No problem to do so on Linux and Windows, but I encountered some
problems when doing so for Termux and Chromebook. This post details
how to resolve the issue on a Chromebook or other locked down
environment.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.NET Core SDK on Debian Testing</title>
      <link>https://matthewemes.com/2017/06/.net-core-sdk-on-debian-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 13:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewemes.com/2017/06/.net-core-sdk-on-debian-testing/</guid>
      <description>Installing .NET Core SDK on Debian Testing tl;dr  install missing packages libicu52, libssl1.0.0 and liblttng-ust0 downgrade curl to stable release 7.38.0-4+deb8u5   Update 6/11/2017:- Accidentally released the hold on curl/libcurl3, and dotnet command still works. I think that libcurl3 is only used when downloading framework and can be reset when done.
 As part of a series of posts on deploying .NET Core applications to GKE, I had to install .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Certified Professional Cloud Architect</title>
      <link>https://matthewemes.com/2017/05/google-certified-professional-cloud-architect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 13:25:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewemes.com/2017/05/google-certified-professional-cloud-architect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I passed my exam to become &lt;strong&gt;Google Certified Professional Cloud
Architect&lt;/strong&gt;! Glad that&amp;rsquo;s out the way, and I can now focus on building
the practice at Neudesic.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m joining Neudesic to build a Google Cloud team</title>
      <link>https://matthewemes.com/2017/04/im-joining-neudesic-to-build-a-google-cloud-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 21:13:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewemes.com/2017/04/im-joining-neudesic-to-build-a-google-cloud-team/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to accept a new challenge, and join the Neudesic team. I&amp;rsquo;m to be their new Director, Google Cloud, helping to build a team ready to work on Google Cloud Platform projects.
Wish me luck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profinder</title>
      <link>https://matthewemes.com/2017/02/profinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 20:44:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewemes.com/2017/02/profinder/</guid>
      <description>I responded to my first Profinder request earlier today, and I am curious to see how well it works in practice. Seems like people simply fill in a form with a few key items, and LinkedIn mines it&amp;rsquo;s database for matching profiles that have signed up for Profinder.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how well this will work out for development projects, as the details as provided by the potential client are not very detailed and I can see how there will be a lot of back and forth in order to create a realistic proposal, but I&amp;rsquo;m willing to give it a shot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>